# Adam Mosebach

Full Stack Web Developer New York. NY

# **Professional Summary**

I am a developer with a passion for thinking outside the box. I believe there are many solutions to achieving a goal and love finding the best one. I am a fun-loving but focused person who finds fulfillment in completing a task. Efficiency and user experience fuel my logical approach to crafting the ideal product.

# **Related Experience**

#### **Software Engineering Immersive Fellow**

General Assembly | New York | 2020-Present

- Built and deployed projects with a React front-end and a MongoDB or Rails backend
- Worked on solo projects as well as in teams, dominated by a creative and collaborative atmosphere
- Daily morning stand-ups with either your team or supervising lead
- Peer review provided alternative solutions to problems

#### **Morgan Stanley**

Programmer | New York | 2006-2007

- Wrote automated processes for incoming trade records to be ingested and analyzed
- Provided error reporting for both the client and Morgan Stanley
- Provided customer service to large firms when further action was needed on client side
- Built a series of training videos to help incoming colleagues perform and onboard efficiently

### Other Work

#### AJ Karaoke

Founder, Owner, Operator | 2014-Present

- Combined many machines to create a full setup for audio and visual technology
- Used Virtual DJ program to implement songs and project lyrics to screen
- Consistently updated the online catalog using a database and elementary php

#### **Professional Actor**

Various Locations | 2007-2019

 Actor (and sometimes assistant stage manager) in various theaters across America, including a national tour and an international tour

## Contact

Phone: 516.721.2784

Email: aimose@aol.com

LinkedIn/in/adammosebach

# **Technical Skills**

JAVASCRIPT REACT

HTML GIT

CSS RUBY

EXPRESS RUBY ON RAILS

NODE.JS POSTGRESQL

MONGO DB COMMAND LINE

MONGOOSE RESPONSIVE DESIGN

### **Education**

# **Certificate of Completion**

General Assembly

New York, NY

#### **Bachelor of Fine Arts**

- minor in Computer Applications

NYU

New York, NY

### **Portfolio**

AdamMosebach.dev